Michelle Bergin Resume

michellejbergin@gmail.com 3604813802 linuxduck.com

Overview

Programmer, Artist, Composer. I program in any language you need, c++, c, java, javascript, lua, prolog, haskell, php, html, css, etc. Also if I don't know it I will learn it! I've worked on cyber security training programs for Edurange.org and my current job is Senior Systems Operator at Evergreen State College. I also have skills in:

- Strong interpersonal communication skills
- Training
- Quality Assurance
- Hiring
- Management
- Sales

Personal Goal

To help with the advancement of AI in turn to help those with neurodivergencies [1]. My personal goal is to replicate human emotions using deep/machine learning. Not to just help with AI, but to learn through our mistakes, what it is to be human. We could then use this information to help those with neurodivergencies.

Skills

Programming Languages / Markup c, c++, lua, java, haskell, prolog, javascript, html, css, LaTeX, Mathematica, bash, powershell, php, angular, ionic, Love2D

Software

Eclipse, git, github, Photoshop, Excel, Word, openscad, arduino ide, terminal, vim/emacs/nano (let's not fight), Sketchup, Dreamweaver, PaintTool SAI, Illustrator, Wireshark, Linux/OSX/Windows, Gimp, etc.

Hardware

Wa
com tablet, VR, 3D Printing, General Tools for building awesome things like robots
 $:\!3!$

Other

Drawing, Sculpting, Composing, Sewing, Robotics, I am a pianist as well.

Work History

Senior Systems Operator - Evergreen State College December 2017 - Present

Programming Internship - Edurange.org (Cyber Security Training) June - August 2018

Companies I worked for were Kress IGA, Office Max, and QFC. I also sold my art regularly and showed my art work at various venues. 2010 - $2016\,$

Quality Management - GoDaddy.com

September 2007 - June 2010

Education

2017 - Present

Evergreen State College Computer Science Expected graduation June 2019 - Bachelor of Science

2015 - 2017

Seattle Central College Computer Science Associates of Science Degree

2001 - 2010

Gateway Community College through Prague College Political Ideologies and Art History Mesa Community College Various classes including GIS, PHP/CGI. South Mountain Community College Gateway Community College

Awards

National Science Foundation S-STEM Scholarship

Recipient at Seattle Central Community College for Spring quarter 2017

Lynda Weinman and Bruce Heavin Endowed Scholarship

Recipient at Evergreen State College for 2018 - 2019

Evergreen Foundation Scholarship

Recipient for 2018 - 2019

References

Sherri Shulman - sherri@evergreen.edu Peter - lynnp@evergreen.edu - 360-867-5555 Richard Weiss - weissr@evergreen.edu - (360) 867-6871

[1] Neurodivergent, sometimes abbreviated as ND, means having a brain that functions in ways that diverge significantly from the dominant societal standards of "normal."